All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I will be the king of the pirates!
Two years have passed since the War of the Best in Marineford.
Reuniting after their special training, Luffy and his crew continue on to the New World.
The first stop on their journey is Fishman Island, thousands of feet below sea level.
However, shortly upon arrival, they found the new Fishman pirates disturbing the peace of the Ryugu Kingdom.
What a horrid thing to do!
Who are you, sir, and what are you doing here?
Please don't hurt me!
Whoa! That's one big lady! I mean, big fish lady!
Someone help me! Brother, please! Brother, please!
Hey, wait! I didn't come here to kill you, okay?
You suck, lady! Shut up!
The Coward and a Crybaby! The Princess and the Hard Shell Tower!
Hey! Stay lit, dimwit!
How many times have I got to tell you that we're working here?
Wait to eat on your own time, you got it?
Oh, yummy!
What?
Is there anything you're neglecting to tell me?
Have you received a reply from Princess Shirahoshi yet?
No!
Sorry, Captain Deakin!
There's still no word!
Just how long has she kept me waiting?
About ten years or so! She's really taking her time!
I don't blame her!
This is the doing of that despicable Neptune!
He intends to force the Princess into a political marriage!
Or so I suspect!
Ten years now!
That heartless monarch has kept his daughter locked in a steel tower for an entire decade!
Oh, how it pains me so!
This cruel tragedy!
The Princess and I are in love!
So!
I suspect!
Princess Shirahoshi!
You are my love!
I love you!
No!
No matter how far I search along this vast sea floor, I will never find another as big
and beautiful as you, my dear!
We are meant to be together!
Yes!
And so!
I'll twist the head off fate itself to prevent you from being with anyone else!
I'd rather see you dead!
Your choice!
You can live as my wife or stop living altogether!
Let me give you another token of my love!
An axe with a rose on it!
Accept this emblem of my deadly undying love!
Ah!
Captain, isn't that the wrong direction?
Don't be a fool!
You know I never miss my target!
Just watch!
Ah!
In reverse course!
And look!
It's heading straight towards the Reagoo Palace!
Ah!
Ha ha!
Hey!
She's so loud!
My ears!
Princess Hero, she's crying!
Get to the Hardshell Tower!
Fine!
But where the hell are the On-Duty Guards?
What?!
So there's nobody protecting her?
I'm sorry sir!
The Guards are in the middle of changing shifts!
No excuses.
To the tower!
Somebody help me please!
There's a human here!
In my chamber!
to the tower somebody help me please there's a human here in my chambers a blood thirsty human
aiming to kill me i'm certain no hey quit making stuff up i just wanted that food i didn't even
know you were in here all right
the heck was that who's throwing axes
jeez come on already where's this banquet i'm getting tired of waiting my stomach is growling
oh hold on i don't even have a stomach the can growl
hey yes i have a funny feeling that this banquet's not happening
what now i thought we'd been pretty good guests so far what's happening i hate to detain you like
this however we've just received a rather distressing call saying that you people
are suspects into ongoing investigation what suspects for what crime first multiple
charges of mermaid kidnapping whoa we would never do something like that second
by reason of madame charlie's premonition your crew is suspected of bringing potential calamity to
fish man island huh wait seriously so you're suspecting us of something that hasn't even happened yet
shut up they need to shut up is this the right course of action based on these charges we will take your
crew into custody do not let them escape protect fish man island at any cost
yeah
scenes there
princess shiroji
what's all that noise sorry
is everything all right princess are you injured somehow
um i'm fine you were crying even louder than usual it gave us quite the fright
hold on the door was already open did you see any intruders here princess
perhaps a strong current opened it i woke crying from a bad dream that's all
i need it i swear i just heard someone uh no that's well um my my stomach was rumbling oh are you
certain who goes there megalo you've returned ah that reminds me i have some rather dire and vexing
information i must relay to you immediately it's regarding the pirate who saved megalo
the one known as straw hat luffy some mermaid girls were kidnapped and he's our prime suspect
also based on a troubling prediction from madam charlie the straw hat crew is considered a potential
risk to the entire kingdom so we've locked them in the palace prison just to be safe
we already have the swordsman in custody upon arrival he drank himself into a state of compliance
three other members of the crew have just arrived and i imagine they're in custody as well by now
but their captain well he might be more perceptive than he appears and picked up on our intentions
for he seems to have fled he is almost certainly hiding somewhere in the palace so please be careful
we'll catch the rest of them on the island in no time i can promise you that we will defend this
country as well as your home at any cost what was that i heard something are you sure you sound
paranoid no i'm sure that i was just your imagination well what i wanted to say i feel awful that we have
to arrest the people who saved megalo i know how much he means to you princess you're acting a bit
strange are you hiding some minister we must leave oh five minutes already well we'll be going now
every lock on those doors you saved me thank you so much i'm sorry i should have given you a
chance earlier i hope you'll forgive me if i had only known who you were that you were the one who
saved megalo not to be overly familiar but may i call you luffy yeah sure so luffy they said that
you're a pirate right does that mean you're a bad person i don't know i think i'll let you make that
call okay oh i don't know if you just heard but our soldiers have taken your friends into custody
yeah that's no big deal trust me on this there's no way your guys can keep them locked up
for long really huh yeah don't worry about it though so what's with the axe let me hear it
you know who threw the thing are they trying to hit you i know who threw it and yes he was
his name is vanderdecken and he's a pirate he wanted to marry me and i refused
so he wants to kill me now and he will there's no escape you see he ate the mark mark fruit
and he used that power to mark me all he has to do is throw a weapon and it will find me anywhere
any time
that's why i never leave here my only real chance to continue living is being locked away inside the
hardshell tower
i'm so hungry
so this creep wants to marry you but he's trying to kill you doesn't make much sense huh
because it's usually one or the other yes i've been in here ten years ten whole years man you
must be bored indeed and my father made a well-meaning but misguided rule so now no one can visit for
more than five minutes which is why megalo's my only real friend without him well i wouldn't have
anyone to talk to yeah they were gonna throw a big banquet to thank us for saving him
that's been cancelled now it's so awful why would they do that they don't have to throw you all in
prison though from what i've heard about madam charlie all of her premonitions have been astoundingly
accurate i suppose that explains the nature of their caution but still
or maybe they were just worried you would consume the entire kingdom's food supply
you humans sure do eat a lot despite how small you are that's the old guy's fault
he made a big fuss about the banquet but then he kept getting yelled at
i finally couldn't wait any longer so i followed the smell here hey by the way did they call you
princess yes so you're the mermaid princess yes that does come with being king neptune's daughter
my name is shira hoshi she what shira hoshi uh that's too tough to say oh i'm eating that
you know i could be wrong but you haven't struck me as a bad person so far are you an adventurer is
that why you decided to become a pirate how wonderful then you must have seen the sun many
times in your adventures oh yeah and what do the stars in the night sky look like oh i bet you've seen
all sorts of animals and flowers too huh now what else oh right have you ever been to the green place i
think perhaps people call it a forest hey relax you ask too many questions just give me a sec
sure it's cute how full your cheeks are
stop it what the heck is wrong with you
please don't please don't yell at me i just can't handle it oh no
you're such a broach calm down this is nothing to cry over stop no one has ever yelled at me before
and i don't like it it's horrible
how can someone so big be such a coward and a cry baby you know i don't think i like you
how could you say that no one's ever said such an awful thing to me you're such a terrible man
please just go i want you to leave i can't take it
it hurts too much
i am full thanks for the grub
well as long as you've been stuck in here no wonder you're scared of everything
leave luffy just please get out of here good but isn't there some place that you want to go
well of course there is there are lots of places that i'd love to see why thought you'd say that
so let's get out of here what let's go take a stroll no i'm not supposed to i can't do that why not
just do it you'll be okay if that guy throws something at you fine i'll take it down just like
the last time
look at this guy passed out sleeping like a baby in a jail cell you didn't see how much booze this
one drink did you hurry up they seem awful worked up what's going on
ussup chin nami chin brook chin
apprehend them now they're just three measly humans don't do anything dumb please you gotta
stop resisting you really will be criminals if you don't yet there is no just cause for them to lock
us up sorry kimi this is such a total letdown i really wanted that banquet at this point playing
nice won't do much good you heard what he said they've made up their minds about what kind of people
we are if they desire we'll stay and fight them till the end of time surely the three of them aren't
that strong they must be bluffing listen up no one knows what the future holds so whether we're heroes
are villains you still shouldn't cross us is it me or has he really gotten his act together
seems like brook chin and nami chin got stronger over the past two years as well
see this is a very prologue to the future that's been foreseen then it's your fault
we wouldn't have fought back in the first place if you guys didn't insist on fighting us
hmm good point but this is nothing not compared to the giant insect attack i went through back when
i was on the bow and islands behold my new weapon black capital i'm happy to give you a demonstration
please keep meptune we need your help
hmm is it really fair to arrest someone based on a prediction that they will commit a crime
i need time to contemplate this it's a precarious situation
and until i decide you will have to wait in custody
okay captain decken this is it just wait for me there waratsumi
sure aye aye aye captain this way of course thanks for your patience
ben decken's here i knew he'd come
welcome sorry to keep you gentlemen waiting we ran into a bit of a volcanic eruption a pity
and you must be the notorious hordy i suspect enough flattery you're notorious
we both are nutty vanderdecken
pleasure to meet you a formal handshake just a moment that's a bit tricky for a fellow like me
uh-huh
there we go
never mind nice to meet you too it's a pleasure mr hordy jones
nothing on the sea floor can stop us now the worst of the worst together at last
of the sea
king neptune is a royal nuisance for you and i alike i'm sure oh yeah we got the same goal here
his army they take no pride in being fishmen so together we will conquer them and then we kill neptune
god of the sea and lastly we will destroy the entire ryuko kingdom
the star hats face off with neptune while they have the upper hand at first neptune's soldiers
threatened to pop their bubble leaving them to drown in the underwater chambers meanwhile luffy and
shira hoshi avoid the pirates attempted infiltration of the tower the peaceful ryugu palace soon devolves
into chaos on the next one piece it's an emergency the ryugu palace is occupied i'm gonna be king of the pirates